I can't even remember that one.
Hi again and welcome to this new video. I think I'm saying this sentence every time. I have to change that.
Hope you're doing fine. This is another haul. I went into Bershka for shopping.
Curious thing is when I go there one time I don't find anything and everything is weird.
And the other time I go into Bershka store and I find a lot of stuff I don't know. It's really weird.
pretty weird. Anyway, let's see what I bought the last time. I just put everything into this box.
All right, this is a bodysuit with some puffy sleeves. In particular, I bought this one to
combine it with these pants. They're a bit baggy style, lots of pockets and cargo pants, that's the
I was looking for. And because I have pants and a bodysuit now I also need a jacket.
Kind of short like only until here. Let's see how everything looks together.
So this is the bodysuit with the cargo pants. I know that there's a trend of
free ankles and the shoes with the pants and space in between. I'm not sure if I
am going to wear that way or I'm going to put on socks to cover my skin and the
legs and black is my favorite color and a happy color so I feel really
comfortable with this outfit so far so I'm going to add the jacket it's a rather
short leather jacket but I like the combination with the pants. It's not a
winter outfit but it's fine for springtime and in the summer you will keep the
leather jacket away but I think it's a cool style and looks nice together. Then
we have a top. I saw this at the store and I thought it's too expensive so I
waited until it was on sale and then I bought it. So the top works with these
pants as well. It's slightly shiny and has proper sleeves and it will work
nicely with leggings and pants and all that kind of stuff. And another jacket.
it's so soft and cuddly it's wonderful I wanna put it in my bed and use it as a pillow
and this is the coziest jacket I own so far it's pretty short
so I have to get used to that and the pockets are like
pretty high. Kind of nice that it's cuddly. It's like I'm cuddling with myself.
Another cuddly and black thing is this cat. Let's combine the cat with the jacket.
And now to the accessories. There is this purse, which is nice and black and small.
small I needed a basic purse which is not too big. I think the purse looks nice
together with the top but I'm kind of confused with the chain so do I have to wear this over
the shoulder or just hang it loose? I don't know. Another chain thingy is this golden hip chain
It's like a belt. I'm not sure how to wear it yet. I hope I can figure it out.
Maybe, wait, there are two coins. There's one. I don't know. I'm confused.
And last but not least, shoes. I bought them on sale because I just thought that they
were discounted and I was like, hey, they look pretty cool and they're like some
sneaker, gothy sneaker, plateau shoes, whatever. In combination with the pants
it's even a bit techwear inspired so I'm sure I'll use them for some photo
shootings of that and I'm like 10 centimeters taller but without a heel
which is pretty good for a night out, partying. So thanks for watching this video
and these were the items I got at Bershka. Tell me if you like these kind of
shopping hauls, if you're interested in them and what else you would like to see
on this channel. I'm open for suggestions and I hope you had fun. Bye, see ya!